Guide to the John Ewart Wallace Sterling, Chancellor of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Series 1
  - Bicentennial
    - The Bureau of International Expositions Memorandum, 1969 Dec. 8 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1970 Feb. 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Letter form Chairman John Gardner on Project '76, 1969 Aug.20 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Letter from the Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Companies, 1970 March 4 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Text of State-of-the-State Message to a Joint Session of the California State Legislature by Reagan, 1970 Jan. 6 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - The National Memorial to Woodrow Wilson: An International Center for Scholars, 1968 June (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Letter from Lindholm. Chairman if D.C. Bicentennial Commission, 1970 Jan. 20 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Letter for Acting President Vandiver of Rice University, 1970 May 11 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia Bicentennial Proposal Revision, 1970 May (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Report to teh American Revolution Bicentennial Commission U.S. Department of Commerce, 1969 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Toward a Meaningful Bicentennial, 1969 Sept. 24 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - A Proposal to the American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1969 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Letters form U.S. Representative Marsh: A Proposal for the Current Establishment of a Federal Commission in Connection with Appropriate Observance of the Bicentennial of the Period of the American Revolution, 1969 Aug.-Sept. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - A Proposal for the American Revolution Bicentennial Celebration, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Proposed American Bicentennial Commemorative Educational Center, 1970 March (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Letter from Henderson Supplee, Jr., 1970 May 6 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Resources Towards a Celebration of the American Experience: A Proposed Model and method of Approach, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Envelope addressed to Sterling, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Info on Nathan H. Mazer and Logistics Spectrum, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - An International Center for the National Capital, 1968 March (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Resolution on Bicentennial Celebration, 1969 Aug. (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Letter from the National Society of the Sons of the American Revolution, 1970 Jan. 13 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - American Revolution Bicentennia; Commission Procedures Manual Draft, 1972 April 27 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Brief Sheet, 1972 May 5 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter: Special Bicentennial Parks Issue, 1970 Feb. 2 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Proposed Plan for Conduct for Achievement Program July 1-Dec 31 1972, 1972 May 31 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Letters form U.S. Representative Lawrence Williams, 1972 May-June (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Report to American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1972 May-July (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Senate Hearings on ARBC Memorandum, 1972 July 21 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence - Ameican Revolution Bicentennial, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Stanford University Libraries Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Copies of Campus Report, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Our American Heritage, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Kaydan Records, 1971 Aug. 27 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - LOOK magazine, 1971 July 13 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Letter from JEJ/gm, 1971 April 23 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Memorandum: International Exposition, 1971 April 20 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - the American Revolution Bicentennial Commission Horizon '76 Committee Revised, 1971 April (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Letter from Blue/Memorandum from Hansen, 1971 May-June (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Memorandum: results of May 26 Philadelpgia Bicentennial Corporation Board Meeting, 1971 May-June (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - An Address to the U.S. Conference of Mayors Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1971 April-June (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Memorandum: Progress Report Concerning Federalism '76, 1971 March-June (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - NY Times: Philadelphia to be a Showcase for U.S. Bicentennial in 1976, 1971 June (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Memorandum: Bicentennial name for Presidential Aircraft, 1971 June 3 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Letter from Spector to Sachar, 1971 May 28 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Letter from hall to Sterling, 1971 June 4 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - American Revolution Minutes of Meeting, 1971 May-June (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Memorandum: Obligations FY 1971, 1971 May 19 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - ARBC News Bulletin, 1971 Sept. 13 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Official Documents of the American Bicentennial Commission, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Memorandum: Proposal by Philadelphia mayor Candidate Longstreth, 1971 Sept. 2 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - ARBC News Bulletin, 1971 Sept. 20 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Sept. 27 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission Meeting Chicago, Illinois, 1971 Oct. 7-8 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Memorandum: Philadelphia Exposition, 1971 July 13 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Memorandum:News Release, 1971 Aug. 13 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Memorandum: Commission Membership, 1971 Aug. 13 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - ARBC News Bulletin, 1971 Aug. 16 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Memorandum: ARBC meeting in Chicago, Illinois on Sept. 23 and 24, 1971, 1971 Aug 2 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Mohoney Letters, 1971 June-July (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Memorandum: Additional Information on Philadelphia, 1971 Aug. 17 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - The Original Signers Medals/The Banker who Bugs Other Bankers, 1971 Oct. (Box 18)
    - LA Times: U.S. Bicentennial Unit Assailed for No Plans, 1971 Dec. 9 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Nov. 29 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Dec. 13 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Advisory Body to the Open House USA Committee, undated (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Memorandum: Advisory Panel on Culture, 1971 July 27 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - ARBC News Bulletin, 1971 Aug. 30 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - ARBC News Bulletin, 1971 Aug. 23 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Membership on Two Standing Advisory Panels for the Open House USA Committee, 1971 July 28 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Memorandum: Nominees for Invitation to the World Advisory Panel, 1971 July 27 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Letter to Keach, 1971 Sept. 1 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - ARBC News Bulletin, 1971 Sept. 6 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Memorandum: July 1971 Activities, 1971 June 4 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Oct. 27 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Oct.18 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Memorandum: Availability of July 3rd TV Program on Film, 1971 Oct. 20 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Oct. 25 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Nov. 1 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Nov. 1 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Memorandum: ARBC Regional Coordinators Indoctrination, 1971 Nov. 4 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Memorandum: Use of Official Symbol by ARBC, 1971 Oct. 21 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Nov. 15 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Dec. 6 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Chances for Bicen Found 50-50; Decision Likely in Med-December, 1971 Dec. 8 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Dec. 20 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Congressional Record, 1971 Dec. 20 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Memorandum,: ARBC Meeting in Dallas, Texas on May 6 and 7, 1971, 1971 Apr 27 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - ARBC Meeting, Dallas Texas Attendees, 1971 may 6-7 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Graphics Manual, 1971 March 25 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Memorandum: Establishment of Roles, 1971 April 27 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Memorandum: Appointment of New ARBC Commissioner, 1971 May 13 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Memorandum: All ARBC Commissioners and Alternates, 1971 May 20 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Roles and Responsibilities of ARBC Draft, 1971 April 20 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 10, 1974 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - New Jersey Historical Commission Newsletter Volume 5, 1974 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 11, 1974 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Minutes: ARBC Full Commission Meeting, 1972 Feb. 21 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - News Bulletin, 1971 Oct. 4 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Memorandum: Summary Report of Executive Committee Meeting of March 21, 1972, 1972 Mar 22 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Memorandum: Minutes of March 21, 1972 Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 Apr 11 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Minutes, 1972 April 20 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 April 20 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Minutes, 1972 May 1 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Transcript of Proceedings, 1972 May 1 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Minutes, 1972 July 24 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - "Call for Achievement": A Plan for a Nationwide Program of Gaol Setting and Achievement by the People of Localities and States, 1972 March (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Members of the Commission, 1972 May 1 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - Changes to List Entitled Members of the Commission, 1972 May 5 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - Memorandum: Full Commission Meeting, 1972 May 15-16 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Schedule and Agenda, 1972 May 15 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Memorandum: My memo of Nov. 11 1971, same subject, 1971 Dec. 3 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - memorandum: Next Full Commission Meeting, 1971 Dec. 15 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Minutes of the American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1971 Dec. 10 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - Films Pamphlet, 1972 Feb, 24 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - Whitehurst Letters, 1971 Aug. 12 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - Congressional Record Vol. 117 No. 186-Part II, 1971 Dec. 2 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Report to the Congress of the United States: American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - The Nation's Birthday I: Celebrations Will Salute Nation's Past Present, and Future, 1973 Jan. 26 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - Copley News Service: Origins of America, 1973 Nov. 6 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 20, 1974 July (Box 18, Folder 126)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 19, 1974 may (Box 18, Folder 127)
    - Bicentennial By-Line No. 2, 1974 April (Box 18, Folder 128)
    - Bicentennial Times Volume 1 Number 8, 1974 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 129)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 9, 1974 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 130)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. III, No. 3, 1973 March (Box 18, Folder 131)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 10, 1972 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 132)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 4 Number 7, 1973 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 133)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Volume III No. 9, 1973 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 134)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 14, 1973 June (Box 18, Folder 135)
    - Bicentennial News, 1973 June 18 (Box 18, Folder 136)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Volume III, No. 7, 1973 July (Box 18, Folder 137)
    - The Correspondent Volume III Number 4, 1973 Spring (Box 18, Folder 138)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Volume III, No. 6, 1973 June (Box 18, Folder 139)
    - Bi-Centennials Gold Theme, 1973 June 5 (Box 18, Folder 140)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Volume III, No. 5, 1973 May (Box 18, Folder 141)
    - Move to Oust Governor, 1973 May 24 (Box 18, Folder 142)
    - The Correspondent Special Edition, 1973 May (Box 18, Folder 143)
    - Bicentennial in Texas Volume 1 Number 3, 1973 Spring (Box 18, Folder 144)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 13, 1973 April (Box 18, Folder 145)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 4 Number 3, 1973 April (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - Bicentennial newsletter Volume 4 Number 4, 1973 May (Box 18, Folder 147)
    - Bicentennial times Volume 1 Number 2, 1974 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - The Correspondent Volume IV Number 2, 1973 Autumn (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 4 Number 8, 1974 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 17, 1974 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - The American Bicentennial newsletter Volume III, No. 12, 1973 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - The American Bicentennial newsletter Volume III, No. 11, 1973 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 153)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV No. 2, 1974 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 154)
    - Bicentennial Times Volume 1 Number 3, 1974 May (Box 18, Folder 155)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 18, 1974 March (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - The Correspondent Volume IV Number 3, 1973 Winter (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 3, 1974 March (Box 18, Folder 158)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 4, 1974 April (Box 18, Folder 159)
    - Bicentennial Times Volume 1 Number 4, undated (Box 18, Folder 160)
    - The Correspondent Volume IV Number 4, 1974 Spring (Box 18, Folder 161)
    - Bicentennial Times Volume 1 Number 6, undated (Box 18, Folder 162)
    - Bicentennial Times Volume 1 Number 5, undated (Box 18, Folder 163)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, no. 5, 1974 May (Box 18, Folder 164)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 6, 1974 June (Box 18, Folder 165)
    - Bicentennial Times Volume 1 Number 7, undated (Box 18, Folder 166)
    - The Correspondent Volume V Number 5, 1974 July-Aug. (Box 18, Folder 167)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 8, 1974, Aug. (Box 18, Folder 168)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 7, 19674 July (Box 18, Folder 169)
    - News Bulletin, 1972 Jan. 17 (Box 18, Folder 170)
    - Bicentennial Era Newsletter Volume 2 Number 7, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 171)
    - Copley News Service, 1971 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 172)
    - News Bulletin, 1972 Jan. 10 (Box 18, Folder 173)
    - Bicentennial Era Newsletter Volume 2 Number 7, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 174)
    - News Bulletin, 1972 Jan. 3 (Box 18, Folder 175)
    - The Correspondent Volume I Number 4, 1971 Spring (Box 18, Folder 176)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Nos. y and 8, 1971 Aug.-Sept. (Box 18, Folder 177)
    - Bicentennial Era Volume 2 Number 4, 1971 May-June (Box 18, Folder 178)
    - The Correspondent Volume II Number 1, 1971 Summer (Box 18, Folder 179)
    - Bicentennial Era Volume 2 Number 5, 1971 July (Box 18, Folder 180)
    - Bicentennial Era Volume 2 Number 4, 1971 May-June (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - Bicentennial Era Newsletter Volume 2 Number 6, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - The Correspondent Volume II Number 2, 1971 Autumn (Box 18, Folder 183)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission Newsletter Volume 1 Number 4, 1974 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 184)
    - Pacific Union Club, 19675 July 1 (Box 18, Folder 185)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission Newsletter Volume1 Number 8, 1975 April (Box 18, Folder 186)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1975 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 187)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1975 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - The Correspondent Volume VI Number 3, 1975 Nov.-Dec. (Box 18, Folder 189)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission newsletter Volume 2 Number 2, 1976 Dec.-Jan. (Box 18, Folder 190)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1976 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - News Report Volume XXVI Number 4, 1976 March (Box 18, Folder 192)
    - News Report Volume XXVI, Number 5, 1976 April (Box 18, Folder 193)
    - The Correspondent Volume VI Number 4, 1976 Jan.-Feb. (Box 18, Folder 194)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1976 March (Box 18, Folder 195)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1976 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 196)
    - The Correspondent Volume VI Number 5, 1976 March-April (Box 18, Folder 197)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Co-mission Newsletter Volume 2 Number 3, 1976 Feb.-March (Box 18, Folder 198)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. II No. 11, 1972 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 199)
    - Bicentennial Bulletins (several issues), 1972 March-Aug. (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - Bicentennial News, 1972 April 30 (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 4, 1972 June (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - Bicentennial news, 1972 April 21 (Box 18, Folder 203)
    - Bicentennial By-Line no. 1, 1972 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. III, No. 1, 1973 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. III No. 2, 1973 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 4 Number 1, 1973 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 207)
    - Bicentennial in Texas Volume 1 Number 2, 1973 Winter (Box 18, Folder 208)
    - The Correspondent Volume III Number 2, 1972 Autumn (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Volume III No. 10, 1973 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 210)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 4 Number 6, 1973 Summer (Box 18, Folder 211)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 4 Number 2, 1970 Feb.2 (Box 18, Folder 212)
    - Bicentennial News, 1973 Dec. 26 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    - Bicentennial Bulletins (Several issues), 1972 Oct.-Nov. (Box 18, Folder 214)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. II No. 12, 1972 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 215)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. II, No. 4, 1972 April (Box 18, Folder 216)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. II, No. 5 (x2), 1972 May (Box 18, Folder 217)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. II, No. 7, 1972 July (Box 18, Folder 218)
    - The American Bicentennial Newsletter Vol. II. No. 8-9, 1972 Aug.-Sept. (Box 18, Folder 219)
    - The American Bicentennial newsletter Vol. II., No. 10, 1972 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 220)
    - Tele-Scope, 1972 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 221)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 1, 1972 March (Box 18, Folder 222)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 2 (x2), 1972 April (Box 18, Folder 223)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 3, 1972 May (Box 18, Folder 224)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter, 1972 July (Box 18, Folder 225)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 2, 1972 April (Box 18, Folder 226)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission Newsletter Volume 1 Number 12, 1975 Aug.-Sept. (Box 18, Folder 227)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1975 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 228)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1975 June (Box 18, Folder 229)
    - The Correspondent Volume v Number 6, 1975 May-June (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission Newsletter Volume 1 Number 9, 1975 May (Box 18, Folder 231)
    - Bicen Iowa, 1975 Aug. (Box 18, Folder 232)
    - The Correspondent Volume VI Number 1, 1975 July-Aug. (Box 18, Folder 233)
    - New Jersey Historical Commission Newsletter Volume 5 Number 10, 1975 June (Box 18, Folder 234)
    - New Jersey Historical Commission Newsletter Volume 5 Number 6, 1975 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 235)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 24, 1975 March (Box 18, Folder 236)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission Newsletter Volume 1 number 5, 1975 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 237)
    - The Correspondent Volume V Number 5, 1975 March-April (Box 18, Folder 238)
    - Continuing Revolution Newsletter, 1975 June (Box 18, Folder 239)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 22, 1975 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 240)
    - The Correspondent Volume V Number 3, 1974 Nov.-Dec. (Box 18, Folder 241)
    - New Jersey Historical Commission Newsletter Volume 5 Number 5, 1975 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 242)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission Newsletter Volume 1 Number 3, 1974 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 243)
    - LA Times: Bicentennial Group Seeking Private Finds, 1974 Dec. 19 (Box 18, Folder 244)
    - New Jersey Historical Commission Newsletter Volume 5 Number 4, 1974 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 245)
    - The American Bicentennial Monthly Volume IV, No. 12, 1974 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - Bicentennial Celebration Commission Newsletter Volume 1 Number 2, 1974 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 247)
    - News Report Vol. XXIV No. 8, 1974 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 248)
    - Bicentennial Iowa Number 21, 1974 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 249)
    - New Jersey Historical Commission Newsletter Volume 5 Number 2, 1974 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - The Correspondent Volume V Number 2, 1974 Sept.-Oct. (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 8 (x2), 1972 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - Bicentennial Newsletter Volume 3 Number 9, 1972 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 253)
    - Envelope of Blank American Bicentennial Commission Papers, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bicentennial Commission Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Bicentennial Commission Correspondence with Commissioners, 1969-1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Bicentennial Commission Correspondence with Congress et al., 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Bicentennial Commission, 1969-1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Godfrey Harris, 1970-1972 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Bicentennial Commission Correspondence, 1969-1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Bicentennial Commission Washington Office, 1969-1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with Studio Watts Workshop, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission Coin and Metals Report #5, 1970 Dec. 24 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Bicentennial Commission Documents, 1966-1970 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Bicentennial Commission Expositions, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Exposition Proposals (Department of Commerce Study), 1970 April 27 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Horizon '76 Committee, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Bicentennial Commission Meetings, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Bicentennial Commission Carlisle H. Humelsine, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - ARBC 2/4-5/71 Meeting, 1971 Jan.-Feb. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Bicentennial Commission Personnel, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Department of Interior American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1969 July 30 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Department of Interior American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1936 July 29 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Bicentennial Commission Organization, 1966-1970 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Bicentennial Commission The Report, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Bicentennial Commission Staff Applicants, 1969-1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Bicentennial Commission Travel Expenses, 1969-1972 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - M.L. Spector (Personal), 1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Staff Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Bicentennial Commission Relations with the White House, 1969-1972 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - State Bicentennial Commissions, 1969-1972 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Bicentennial -- California Commission, 1968-1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Bicentennial Commission Publicity, 1969-1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Bicentennial ERA Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Bicentennial Commission National Governors' Conference, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Colorado Springs, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University
    - Stanford Alumni Association Executive Board 1967-1968, 1968 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Alumni Association Executive Board 1968-1969, 1969 Feb. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Alumni Association Executive Board 1968-1969, 1969 May (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Alumni Association Executive Board 1969-1970, 1970 Feb. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Alumni Opinion Wave 1, 1969 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - North American Agricultural Exports to The United Kingdom: Some Preliminary Indications of the Effects of British Entry Into the EEC, 1969 Dec. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Herbert Hoover Public Positions and Honors, 1964 July (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - The Herbert Hoover Presidential Library, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume 1 - No. 7, 1973 Sept. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume 2 - No. 5, 1974 Jan. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume II - No. 1, 1974 May (Box 19, Folder 11)